

HELO, MY NAME IS CONORCRES FILUSTRATOR

NFL Enthusiast | Video Game Player Person | Book Reader | Music Player and Listener | Film Nerd

EXPERIENCE

Sprechen Digital Marketing Graphic Designer and Illustrator (March 2015 to April 2017)

Bravo Post Production Graphic Designer and Animator/Runner (June 2015 to July 2015)

EDUCATION

BA Digital Media Design (Sept 2013 to October 2016) Graduated with 1st Class Honours

MA Digital Media Practice (September 2016 to October 2017) Graduating in October 2018

CONTACT

59 Titchfield Park Road, Fareham, Hampshire PO15 5RN

07808 274195 conorcresswell94@gmail.com conorcresswell.github.io

ABOUT

A self-motivated individual underpinned with a strong work ethic with an ambitious approach to life both professionally and personally. With two years of experience in Freelance Graphic Design and Illustration services using the Adobe Creative Suite with a focus on Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop and InDesign.

Mixed in with a first-class undergraduate degree in Digital Media Design and undertaking a post-graduate degree in Digital Media Practice. A young, confident designer in their field who will always enjoy undertaking challenging and pushing projects without being afraid to do something different.

KEY SKILLS

Confident ability to create vector illustrations using Adobe Illustrator

Strong ability in Adobe InDesign and Photoshop to create effective and informative documents

Practical Experience in using HTML and CSS Frameworks to create one-page websites

Experience in optimising content for websites and Content Management Systems such as Wordpress

Confidence in presenting ideas to clients and team members